mgm.com 2011-12-05

# The Official Website for Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer (MGM) Studios: Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

_Effective Date: February 6th, 2008_

This web site (the "Site") is owned by Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer Studios Inc. or one of its subsidiary or affiliated companies, including Orion Pictures Corporation and United Artists Films Inc. (collectively, "MGM" or "we," "us" or "our"). This Privacy Policy discloses our information and privacy practices with regard to the Site, such as the types of information we may gather from you and other visitors to the Site ("Site Visitors") and how we may use and share that information. Except if specifically stated otherwise, this Privacy Policy applies only to information collected on the Site and does not apply to information collected offline or otherwise outside of the Site. 

Please take a moment to review the terms of this Privacy Policy. By using the Site, you agree to accept the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site. Please also review the [Terms of Use](http://www.mgm.com/terms_of_use.php), which governs your use of the Site. Please note that certain features or services discussed in this Privacy Policy may not be offered on the Site at any particular time

IN CASES WHERE WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN UNDER 13, WE FOLLOW SPECIAL ADDITIONAL PROCEDURES, AS SET FORTH IN THE CHILDREN'S PRIVACY SECTION BELOW.

### THE SITE'S COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION: 

MGM may ask you to provide us with "personal information" (which shall mean information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, e-mail address, telephone number, or home address) while you are on the Site, and we may require you to provide personal information if you choose to participate in certain of the Site's features. For example, we may collect personal information when you register on the Site; submit information needed to consider you for potential employment opportunities; participate in contests, sweepstakes, events or promotions offered through the Site; subscribe to our online newsletter, bulletins or other online services; send questions or comments to us or fill out online or e-mail surveys. We may also collect certain demographic information (such as gender or age) and information about your interests and preferences ("preferences information"). In many cases, such preferences information is optional. If we ever use any preferences information together with any personal information, then such preferences information will be treated as personal information under this Privacy Policy.

We retain and use your personal and preferences information in order to provide you with services or fulfill transactions that you have requested; facilitate your job search and prepare governmental and internal statistics reports; send you newsletters and other e-mail communications for which you have subscribed or agreed to receive; communicate with you regarding information, features or offers that we believe will be of interest to you; contact you regarding a sweepstakes, contest or promotion in which you have participated; respond to your questions or other requests; contact you with regard to your use of the Site or, in our discretion, changes to the Site's Privacy Policy, Terms of Use or other Site policies; or for other purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information. We may also use such personal and preferences information to improve the Site and its content, features and services; customize your experience on the Site; or for other internal business purposes. 

Please note that information submitted to the Web Site via a "contact us," "help" or other similar mechanism will not necessarily receive a response. We will not use the information provided to these mechanisms to contact you for marketing purposes unrelated to your request.

If you submit to MGM and/or the Site comments, photographs, videos, music, text or other content, it maybe published online or offline (including on-air, in a DVD, or any other format currently existing or hereafter developed); we may publish your name, voice, likeness and other personal information in connection with publishing the content or a portion of the content; and we may use the content and any excerpt from the content in connection with advertising, marketing, publicity and promotional activities. Please also see the "Submissions" section of our Terms of Use, which governs any content you submit through the Site or to MGM.

For some features of the Site, you may be able to submit information about other people. For example, if you wish to send an e-mail or e-postcard to a friend from the Site, you will submit your friend's e-mail address. We will use the information that we collect from you about another person to carry out your request, and we will not use such information for any other marketing purpose.

In addition to the foregoing, from time to time we may obtain personal information that has been collected by third parties. We may use such personal information in combination with personal information that we have collected from you on the Site, in which case we will apply this Privacy Policy to such. However, because this personal information is not collected on the Site, we are not responsible for the accuracy of this personal information or how such third parties collect and use this personal information.

### INFORMATION RELATED TO USE OF OUR SITE; AGGREGATE INFORMATION:

We may collect certain information about your visits to our Site; your transactions with us, sites that link to us, or sites to which we link; and your Site usage patterns, such as the pages on the Site you have visited and the amount of time you have spent on our Site. In some cases, we may link this information to personal information that you have provided to us in order to better tailor the Site and its services to your needs and preferences. To collect this information, we may log your IP address and we may use cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies (web beacons, cookies and IP addresses are discussed further below). Such information enables us to better customize our content and services to Site Visitors' needs. We may group this information into non-personally identifiable aggregate Site Visitor data in order to describe the use of our Site to our existing or potential business partners, sponsors, advertisers or other third parties. We also reserve the right to use cookies, IP addresses and other tracking technologies to identify a Site Visitor when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our Site's policies; to protect our Site, Site Visitors or others; or in cooperation with law enforcement.

**Cookies**

Many of our web pages use "cookies." MGM does not save personal information in cookies, but we may link cookies to any personal information or other information we collect. You have the option of disabling cookies using your browser's preferences. However, please be aware that some features of the Site may not function properly or may be slower if you refuse cookies.

**IP Addresses**

An IP address is a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are browsing the Web. Web servers, the big computers that "serve up" Web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address. When Site Visitors request pages from the Site, our servers log the Site Visitors' IP addresses.

**Web Beacons**

Our web pages or e-mail messages may contain a small graphic image called a web beacon, which is sometimes also called a "clear gif," that allows us to monitor and collect certain limited information about our users, such as the type of browser requesting the web beacon, the IP address of the computer that the web beacon is sent to, and the time the web beacon was viewed. Web beacons can be very small and invisible to the user, but, in general, any electronic image viewed as part of a web page or e-mail, including HTML based content, can act as a web beacon. We may use web beacons to count visitors to our Site or to monitor how Site Visitors navigate our Site, and we may include web beacons in email messages in order to count how many messages we sent were actually opened or acted upon.

### HOW THE SITE SHARES PERSONAL INFORMATION:

The Site may share non-personally identifiable information, such as aggregated user statistics, with third parties. The Site does not share your personal information with third parties for those third parties' marketing purposes unless you have opted-in or chosen not to opt-out from such sharing as set forth below. In addition, MGM may share your personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy or in the following limited circumstances: 

We sometimes use other businesses to perform certain services for us, such as web site hosting, sending e-mail or other communications, fulfilling orders, providing marketing assistance and data analysis, clearing and processing credit card payments, or performing other administrative services. We may provide personal information in to such service providers in order for them to complete a requested transaction or otherwise perform their duties for MGM.

During the course of registering on our Site, entering sweepstakes or otherwise providing us your personal information, we may ask you if you would like us to share your personal information with identified third parties in order to offer or provide you with additional information, products or services. We will not share your personal information without your consent, which you may give by opting in to such sharing or choosing not to opt out of such sharing (depending on the particular area of the Site on which you are given the opportunity to provide your consent). If you consent to our sharing your information with identified third parties, then from time to time, you may receive communications from such third parties, such as promotional offers available from such businesses. Further, if you do agree to have your personal information shared, all information you disclose will be subject to the privacy policy and practices of such third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of such third parties and, therefore, you should review the privacy policies and practices of such third parties prior to agreeing to receive such information from third parties. If you later decide that you no longer want to receive communication from a third party, you will need to contact that third party directly.

If you choose to enter a sweepstakes, contest or other promotion, your personal information may be disclosed to third parties in connection with the administration of such promotion, including, without limitation, in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law, such as on a winners list. Also, by entering a promotion, you are agreeing to the official rules that govern that promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you, including, except where prohibited by law, allowing the sponsor(s) of the promotion to use your name, voice and/or likeness in advertising or marketing associated with the promotion.

In conjunction with laws and regulations enforced by the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission ("EEOC"), the Office of Federal Contract Compliance Programs ("OFCCP") and similar state and local regulatory agencies, we may ask you to provide us with self-identifying information (such as veteran status, gender and ethnicity). Providing such self-identifying information is voluntary, but if you do provide us with such information, we may submit that information, to the EEOC, the OFCCP and similar state and local regulatory agencies for business-related purposes, including, but not limited to responding to information requests, fulfilling regulatory reporting requirements and defending against employment related complaints.

We also reserve the right to transfer and disclose information, including your personal information and IP address, to third parties to comply with a legal obligation; when we believe in good faith that the law requires it; at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation; to verify or enforce our Terms of Use or other applicable Site policies; to respond to an emergency; or otherwise to protect the rights, property, safety, or security of third parties, Site Visitors or the public.

MGM reserves the right, and you consent to, the disclosure, transfer and subsequent use of your information, including personal information, to a subsequent owner, co-owner or operator of the Site or the applicable MGM database, or in the event MGM (or any of its affiliated, parent or subsidiary companies) assigns its rights and obligations regarding any of your information to a third party or in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, restructuring, the sale of substantially all of our assets, or other corporate change.

### ADVERTISEMENTS AND THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING COMPANIES

We may use information about you and your visits to the Site in order to serve advertisements to you on our web pages. We may also use a third party advertising company to serve ads to you. We or our third party advertising companies may note the pages you visit on the Site through the use of web beacons or cookies placed on your computer to manage and target advertisements and for market research analysis. We may share non-personally identifying web site usage information about visitors to the Site with third party advertising companies for the same purposes.

In addition, when you are on this Site, third party advertising companies may be able to place a unique cookie on your computer for the purpose of targeting advertisements to you when you are visiting this or other web sites. These cookies are used to aggregate historical behaviors in order to deliver ads to you that are likely to be more relevant to you based on the types of web sites visited. A third-party advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, which may differ from this one. We do not have access to cookies set by third parties.

### CHANGING YOUR PREFERENCES AND UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION:

Users who receive the MGM newsletter or other similar e-mails from us regarding MGM properties and who wish to remove themselves from this mailing list can do so by following the link provided in an e-mail received, or by visiting the "unsubscribe" page on the main MGM.com site, located at [www.mgm.com/register/newsletter_unsubscribe.php](http://www.mgm.com/register/newsletter_unsubscribe.php). However, even if you opt-out from receiving the MGM newsletter or similar e-mails from us regarding MGM properties, we reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to our Site, such as service announcements, notices of changes to this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use or similar administrative or transactional messages, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.

### LEAVING THE SITE:

Please be aware that when you are on our Site, you could be directed to other sites that are operated by third parties and beyond our control. For example, our Site provides links to third party sites through which you can purchase merchandise, products or services or participate in blogs, message boards or similar Forums. These links may include links from sponsors or partners that use an MGM logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other third parties may send their own cookies to visitors, collect data or solicit personal information. You acknowledge that we do not monitor or control the information collection or privacy practices of these or any other third parties, and are not responsible for their practices or the content of their web sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of such third parties to understand how they collect and use information.

### PUBLIC FORUMS:

We may provide chat rooms, message boards and other "public" forums on our Site for discussing various topics (collectively, the "Forums"). Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information on a Forum, that information can be collected and used by people you do not know. If you choose to voluntarily disclose information on a Forum, the protections of this Privacy Policy will not cover such disclosure of information. We urge you to use caution when disclosing any personal information on a Forum. We are not responsible and will not be liable for any opinions, content or other materials posted by Site Visitors on any such Forums, or for the use by other Site Visitors or third parties of any information or content you may post to such Forums. Your use of Forums is subject to our Code of Conduct and other provisions of the Terms of Use.

### SECURITY:

While MGM strives to secure your personal information and privacy, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure or hacker proof. Please consider this when you choose the information, if any, you wish to transmit to the Site or to MGM through the Internet.

### REVISIONS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY:

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes to this Privacy Policy by posting a notice on the homepage of our Site that this Privacy Policy has been updated for a reasonable period of time after such changes are made, and by changing the "Effective Date" at the top of this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to check periodically for any changes. However, we will use your personal information in a manner consistent with the Privacy Policy in effect at the time you submitted the information, unless you consent to the new or revised policy.

### GOVERNING LAW, VISITORS RESIDING OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES,

### AND CONSENT TO TRANSFER:

This Privacy Policy and the privacy practices of MGM will be subject exclusively to the laws of the State of California within the United States of America, without regard to its conflict of law principles. MGM makes no representation that this Privacy Policy and such practices comply with the laws of any other country. Visitors who use the Site and reside outside the United States do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable. If you are located in the European Union, Canada or elsewhere outside of the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using the Web Sites or providing us with your information, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to this Privacy Policy and to the collection, storage, and processing of such information in the United States of America.

### CHILDREN'S PRIVACY:

This Site is a general audience website that does not knowingly collect personal information from children younger than 13 ("Children"). If, however, MGM offers a feature that is directed to Children or knowingly collects personal information from via this Site, any personal information submitted by Children will be collected and maintained in accordance with the Children's Online Protection Act ("COPPA"). To assist parents in supervising their Children's online activities,, MGM has adopted the following special policies for Children's privacy. MGM urges kids to check with their parents before submitting information to any web site. To the extent that any terms of this Children's Privacy section conflict with any of the foregoing terms of this Privacy Policy, the terms of this section will control with regard to the personal information of Children.

**Collection and Use of Information**

If the Site linking to this Privacy Policy is directed to Children or if the Site knowingly collects personal information from Children, the personal information collected from Children may be used to provide services for which the Child has subscribed, respond to a Child's questions or other requests, or otherwise enter the Child in MGM Site activities, such as sweepstakes or contests. MGM does not require Children to disclose more information for an online activity than is reasonably necessary for that Child to participate in the online activity.

**Parental Notice and Consent**

Except in limited circumstances allowed by COPPA and discussed in the section immediately below, MGM will not knowingly collect, maintain, or use any personal information from a Child without first providing notice to the Child's parent or legal guardian and obtaining their consent.

**Exceptions to Parental Notice and Consent**

Under certain circumstances, MGM may not provide parental notice and/or obtain parental consent. For example:

**One Time Use:** MGM may collect a child's e-mail address for the sole purpose of responding to the child's request or communicating with the child on a one-time-only basis. Examples include responding to a question or notifying a Child that the Child has won a sweepstakes or contest. In these instances, MGM will not provide notice and obtain consent from parents prior to contacting the child; however, we will not use the personal information collected to recontact the child and we will delete the personal information from our records. With regard to sweepstakes, contests and promotions, we will obtain written parental consent before sending any prizes to contest winners or posting any information about winners on the MGM Site who are Children.

**Multiple Contacts Based on a Single Request:** MGM may collect a child's e-mail address in order to respond directly more than once to a specific request from the child (for example, where a child registers for the MGM newsletter). In such cases, MGM will attempt to notify the child's parent(s) or legal guardian(s) after first contacting the Child, and will give the parent(s) or legal guardian(s) the ability to opt-out of MGM's further use of the Child's information. Prior to any other collection or use of personal information from a child under 13, MGM shall obtain a parent's consent to such collection and use in accordance with COPPA. We may seek a parent's consent to collect information such as a child's name, mailing address, e-mail address, etc.

**Sharing of Information**

The personal information collected from Children will not be shared or forwarded by MGM to business partners, advertisers or other third parties without a parent's prior consent, except: (i) as required or permitted by law, (ii) to protect the security or integrity of the MGM Site; and (iii) to trusted third parties who provide support for the internal operations of the Site, such as preparing and delivering newsletters; however, these third parties are not authorized to use or disclose such personal information for any other purpose.

**Parental Access**

Parents of Children may at any time review the personal information about their Children that we have collected, refuse to allow any further collection or use of their Children's personal information, or have their Children's personal information deleted from our records. If you would like to review or delete your child's personal information, please contact us at [kidsprivacy@mgm.com](mailto:kidsprivacy@mgm.com). When a parent requests deletion of his or her Child's personal information, we will use reasonable efforts to delete as much of the Child's personal information from our database as possible and refrain from collecting any other personal information from such Child. However, there may be residual information that will remain within our database that may or may not contain personal information, but will not be used for any commercial purpose.

### Web Site Operator:

Name: Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer Studios Inc.  
Address: 10250 Constellation Boulevard, Los Angeles, California 90067-6241  
Phone: 310-449-3000   
E-mail Address: [comments@mgm.com](mailto:comments@mgm.com)

© 2011 Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer Studios Inc.
